Finding Aid for D. James Galbraith Photographic Collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
D. James Galbraith photographic collection 1955-2012, 1968-1993
Galbraith, D. James.
1 oversize portfolio
6 oversize boxes
(in 10 boxes)
16 linear feet
2013006 Aa 2
The D. James Galbraith Photographic Collection reflects D. James (Jim) Galbraith's career as a photographer, covering more than five decades and containing thousands of pictures in the form of prints, negatives, and slides about everyday life in rural Michigan. The D. James Galbraith Photographic Collection is significant for its extensive photographic evidence of rural Michigan, particularly its emphasis on families, communities, and local institutions such as churches and schools. The collection is useful as a visual representation of late twentieth-century Michigan, capturing a wide array of social and cultural activities that highlight the daily experiences of Michigan residents.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was received from Susan Galbraith (Donor no. 10901) in three accessions between June and September 2012.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
D. James (Jim) Galbraith (1930-2002) was a photographer who is noted for documenting life in Hartland, Michigan. Galbraith was born May 26, 1930 in Ann Arbor, Mich., and later attended Ann Arbor High School. At the onset of the Korean War, the United States Air Force drafted Galbraith into its ranks shortly after his graduation and stationed him in Alaska as an aerial photographer. He enrolled in courses at the University of Alaska (Fairbanks) but left before completing his degree.
Galbraith used the photography skills he acquired in the military to begin a successful career as a photojournalist for the Ann Arbor News. His first published photograph, a picture of two men at the New York Central Railroad stop in Ann Arbor entitled "Waiting for the Morning Train," graced the newspaper's front cover on November 12, 1954. Galbraith spent the next three decades of his career with stints between the Ann Arbor News, the Brighton Argus and the Livingston County Press.
During the course of his career, Galbraith also devoted time to several professional organizations, including the Hartland Art Council (Chairperson and Board Member), Metro Detroit News Photographers' Association (Vice President), and the Michigan Press Photographers' Association (President and Board of Directors). Other memberships included the Michigan Oral History Council, the Ann Arbor Art Association, and the American Association for State and Local History. In addition, Galbraith delivered guest lectures at the Center for Creative Studies (Detroit), the University of Michigan, and Washtenaw Community College.
Following a successful career as a photojournalist, Galbraith embarked on a career as a commercial photographer, opening his own studio, Galbraith Photography, in East Jordan, Mich. His 1985 book Hartland: Change in the Heart of America garnered a Pulitzer Prize nomination for Photo documentary. His photographic work was accepted and displayed in countless juried art competitions across the country; among them the 1988 Ann Arbor State Street Art Festival for which he was awarded the Purchase Award. Galbraith photographed not only families, schools, churches throughout the state of Michigan but also was commissioned for artists such as Aaron Copland and Dame Judith Anderson.
On July 21, 2002 Galbraith died in Antrim County, Mich. at the age of 72. Since his death, art galleries and art exhibitions have continued to showcase Galbraith's work.
The D. James Galbraith Photographic Collection is a selection of his work that primarily contains prints, negatives, and slides. The content of Galbraith's photographs is vast, but most reflect various aspects of everyday life throughout the state of Michigan. The collection is arranged into four series: Business Records, Hartland Project, and Private Photography, and Oversize.
Subjects:
Galbraith, D. James.; Galbraith, D. James.--Hartland: change in the heart of America.; Families.; Farm life--Michigan.; Weddings.; Hartland (Mich.); Michigan--Social life and customs--20th century.
Genre Terms:
Black-and-white prints (photographs); Negatives.; Photographs.; Slides (photographs)
- Business Records 1960-2012
  The Business Records series has materials documenting the business transactions that accompanied many of Galbraith's projects and clients. Covering the years 1960-2012 files in this series are arranged chronologically and cover everything from client recommendations to correspondence discussing Galbraith's Pulitzer Prize nomination. The materials generated after his 2002 death are primarily exhibit programs and descriptions gathered at public displays of his work.
  - Reviews and Testimonials 1960-2000 (scattered) (Box 1)
  - Clippings 1967-2010 (scattered) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence 1983-1986 (Box 1)
  - Touring 1983-1985 (Box 1)
  - Photo Consent Forms 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Resumes and Biographical Materials 1985-2010 (Box 1)
  - Certificates 1986, undated (Box 1)
  - Interview with Jim Galbraith and Glenn Ruggles 2000 (Box 1)
  - Exhibit Announcements and Programs 2001-2012 (scattered and undated, see also oversize) (Box 1)
  - Promotional Materials undated (Box 1)
  - Photos of Jim Galbraith undated (Box 1)
  - (see oversize) (Box 1)
- Hartland Project
  Included in the Hartland Project series are hundreds of prints, slides, negatives, and draft materials that became part of Galbraith's book Hartland: Change in the Heart of America. The folders containing inventories are indicated in the contents list, with the majority of photographs taken in the years just before the book's publication. Folders are arranged according to their format as prints, negatives, and slides.
  - Black and white 8 x 10 Project Photo Prints (Inventory included undated in 10 folders) (Box 1)
  - 11 x 14 black and white matted prints undated (Box 2)
  - 11 x 14 black and white framed prints undated (Box 3)
  - Black and white 8 x 10 Project Photo Prints (Inventory included undated in 5 folders) (Box 4)
  - Black and white 8 x 10 Project Photo Prints, (undated in 8 folders) (Box 4)
  - Project Draft Materials 1985, undated (Box 4)
  - Project Slides 1979-1985, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Project Negatives 1980-1985, 3 folders (Box 5)
- Private Photography 1955-1994
  The Private Photography series is the most extensive within the collection and spans 1955-1994 with a majority of items undated. It is divided into the following subseries: Ann Arbor Weddings and Families; Clients; Commissions and Events; Life in Michigan; and Mostly Michigan Exhibit. The Ann Arbor Weddings and Families subseries is arranged chronologically. Many, but not all, individual photograph sleeves within folders contain labels indicating names and/or places. The Clients subseries has two arrangements, one chronological by year and the other alphabetical by name or topic. The photographs in this subseries are primarily slides and 4 x 5 negatives, though a few are 8 x 10 prints. The item's contents differ greatly, but one can find many family and school portraits in the subseries. The Commissions and Events subseries follows a chronological arrangement and includes entertainers such as Ruby Dee, Benny Goodman, and Bert Lahr and as well as literary figures such as Dudley Randall and Arthur Miller. The Life in Michigan subseries has 7 x 10 and 8 1/2 x 11 prints from Galbraith's travels through Michigan. There are no dates attached to any of the folders or items in the subseries.
  - Ann Arbor Weddings and Families (Negatives)
    - 1955-1963
      - Bishop, Matt (Box 5)
      - Freeman, Larry (Box 5)
      - Fiedler, A. (Box 5)
      - McCoy, Lester (Box 5)
      - Gilbert, Peter and Shirley (Box 5)
      - Conlin, Elizabeth and Greg (Box 5)
      - St. Andrew (?) (Box 5)
      - Mikado Principals (Box 5)
    - 1964-1965
      - Morningstar, Gershom (Box 5)
      - Plummer, David H. (Box 5)
      - Oliver Family Group (Box 5)
      - Riecker Family (Box 5)
      - Stranahan, Duane (Box 5)
      - Towsley, Susan (Box 5)
      - Schïlp Project (Box 5)
      - Kimmel, Kathleen (Box 5)
    - 1966
      - Anderson, Dame Judith (Box 5)
      - Barron, Connie (Box 5)
      - Bemevento, Elena (Box 5)
      - Brooks, Jacqueline (Box 5)
      - Carparelli, Anna (Box 5)
      - Cicierska, Margaret (Box 5)
      - O'Brian, Francis (Box 5)
      - Paisner, Dina (Box 5)
      - Servin, Bruce (Box 5)
    - 1967
      - Alice Children in Howell (Box 5)
      - Amato, Julie (Box 5)
      - Burgess, Rick (Box 5)
      - Consumers Powers Co. (Box 5)
      - Craig Bride Portrait (Box 5)
      - Crandall, Richard (Box 5)
      - Conlin, William (Family) (Box 5)
      - Dreyfus, Pixie (Box 5)
      - Galbraith Personal (Box 5)
      - Jones, Ann (Box 5)
      - Masonic Groups (Box 5)
      - Mersereau and Jumping Horse (Box 5)
      - Minch, Susan Galbraith (Box 5)
      - Oliver, Scott (Box 5)
      - Oliver Family (Box 5)
      - Wesson, V.R. (Box 5)
    - 1968
      - Baldwin, Pete (Box 5)
      - Dr. Bethea (Box 5)
      - Chicago L. Symphony (Box 5)
      - Citizens Mutual (Box 5)
      - Collins, John L. (Box 5)
      - Consumer Power (Box 5)
      - Conlin-Claims Landscape (Box 5)
      - Conlin, William (Family) (Box 5)
      - Dibble, Riecker (Wedding) (Box 5)
      - Edie and Jim (Box 5)
      - Edie and Kid (Box 5)
      - Electric Apparatus (Box 5)
      - Farm Bureau (Box 5)
      - First Federal Savings and Loan (Box 5)
      - Ford Garland (Box 5)
      - I.B.M. (Box 5)
      - Kleeb, Robert (Box 5)
      - Kutge Wedding (Box 5)
      - Lancer Arabians (Box 5)
      - Dr. May (Sullivan Infant) (Box 5)
      - McPherson Bank (Box 5)
      - McPherson Health Center (Box 5)
      - McPherson Hospital (Box 5)
      - McPherson House (Box 5)
      - P.T.P. The Castle (Box 5)
      - Roadway, Inc. (Box 5)
      - Samra, Paul N. (Box 5)
      - Schneider, Elmer (House) (Box 5)
      - Trinity Church Confirmation (Box 5)
      - Mrs. Squires (Box 5)
      - Thomas, Leigh (Box 5)
    - 1969
      - Baldwin, Pete (Box 5)
      - Belyea (Box 5)
      - Campbell, Doris (Sally's Wedding) (Box 5)
      - Concept Development Corp. (Box 5)
      - Hahn Wedding (Box 5)
      - Haigh Mtg. (Box 5)
      - Don Hall (Box 5)
      - Karapatian Family and Wedding (Box 5)
      - Ketchern, Russ (Box 5)
      - Lancer Arabians (Box 5)
      - Lloyd, Cindy (Box 5)
      - McPherson Health Center (Box 5)
      - Nobillette, Doug and Dot (Box 5)
      - Shaner Wedding (Box 5)
      - Trinity Lutheran Church Confirmation (Box 5)
      - Walker, Jackie (Box 5)
      - Wright, Willy (Box 5)
    - 1970
      - Baldwin, Gary (Box 5)
      - Coulin (Box 5)
      - Whitman, James (Box 5)
    - 1972
      - Oliver, Dr. William (Family) (Box 5)
    - 1973
      - Hyne Wedding (Box 5)
    - 1974
      - Beckett-Mossberg Wedding (Box 5)
      - Chuck & Barbara Sturn Wedding (Box 5)
    - 1975
      - Forsythe Show (Box 5)
    - Undated
      - Bender, David (Box 6)
      - Bender, Kim (Box 6)
      - Bender, Nancy (Box 6)
      - Kettlhut Wedding (Box 6)
      - McIver, Andrew (Box 6)
      - Reicker, John (Box 6)
      - Wolf, Gerald (Box 6)
      - Yoder, Dr. O.R. (Box 6)
      - Unidentified (Box 6)
  - Clients (Negatives and Prints)
    - 1972
      - Beltz, Mary Ann (Box 6)
      - Brighton State Bank (Box 6)
      - Eisenhart, Libby (Box 6)
      - Nolling-Merriman Real Estate (Box 6)
      - Northville Record Building (Box 6)
      - Phelps, Hines (Box 6)
      - Schriber, Allan (Box 6)
    - 1973
      - Capital Ade (Box 6)
      - Green, Dorothy (Box 6)
      - Kane, Mr. (Box 6)
      - McGuire, William (Box 6)
      - Pooley, Pat (Box 6)
      - Radinoth, Dr. (Family Passports) (Box 6)
      - West Oakland Bank (Box 6)
      - Xerox Corporation (Box 6)
    - 1974
      - Barron, Francis (Box 6)
      - Bender, Kim (Box 6)
      - Beverly Manor (Box 6)
      - Brighton State Bank (Box 6)
      - Caldwell, Rich (Box 6)
      - Day, Jim (Box 6)
      - Gregory, David (Box 6)
      - Henrick, Bert (Box 6)
      - Hicks, Mr. and Mrs. (Passport) (Box 6)
      - Interlochen School Office (Box 6)
      - Jeffrey, Julie (Box 6)
      - Livonia Bar Association Officers (Box 6)
      - McIntyre, Elaine (Box 6)
      - Kimball & Russell, Inc. (Box 6)
      - Kleeb, Robert (Box 6)
      - Mackinac Island (Box 6)
      - Mahinski, Paul (Box 6)
      - McDermott, John (Box 6)
      - Munsell, Erica (Box 6)
      - Northville Lab (Box 6)
      - Parker, Donna Scott (Box 6)
      - Schonely, Gene (Box 6)
      - School of Education (University of Michigan) (Box 6)
      - South Lyon High School Band (Box 6)
      - Sturn, David (Box 6)
    - 1975
      - Arendt, Walker (Box 6)
      - Balanger Inc. (Box 6)
      - Baldwin, Luke (Box 6)
      - Cannarelli, Fred (Box 6)
      - Cannon, Sherrie (Box 6)
      - Cross, Jay (Box 6)
      - Evans, Kim (Box 6)
      - Fader, Dan (Box 6)
      - Haviland Pointers (Box 6)
      - Lavan, Martin (Box 6)
      - Hunt, Milo (Box 6)
      - MPPA (Box 6)
      - Pennock, Mrs. Gilbert (Box 6)
      - Phelps Hines (Box 6)
      - Truance, Sam (Box 6)
      - Tolaben-Lamage Birth (Box 6)
      - Westerman, Charlie (Box 6)
      - Zayti Trucking (Box 6)
    - 1976
      - 1st National Bank Howell (Box 6)
      - 1st Federal Show (Box 6)
      - Ambler, Jean (Box 6)
      - Belanger Car Wash (Box 6)
      - Belize Street Band (Box 6)
      - Bourne, Lyn (Box 6)
      - Brighton Township Firehall (Box 6)
      - Carney, Brent (Box 6)
      - Cars & Concepts Inc. (Box 6)
      - Carver, Larry (Box 6)
      - DeCris Construction (Box 6)
      - Farington House (Box 6)
      - Gee, David (Box 6)
      - Greek Revival House (Box 6)
      - Haviland, Nancy (Box 6)
      - Hi-Q Inc. (Box 6)
      - Howell Baseball Team (Box 6)
      - Kachelko, Frank (Box 6)
      - Kreewall, Ed (Box 6)
      - LaVasseur, Debbie (Box 6)
      - Murphy, Raymond (Box 6)
      - Northville Garden Club (Box 6)
      - Northville Labs (Box 6)
      - Novi "Choralires" (Box 6)
      - Shill, Mike (Box 6)
      - South Lyon Middle School Band & Choir (Box 6)
      - South Lyon High School Band (Box 6)
      - The Ark (Box 6)
      - Young, Lori (Box 6)
    - 1977
      - Belenger, Inc. (Box 6)
      - Church Exterior (Box 6)
      - Cowan, Judy (Box 6)
      - Cox, Buster (Box 6)
      - Englehardt Family Group (Box 6)
      - Fisher, Grant (Box 6)
      - Giermanm, Cookie (Box 6)
      - Goodman, Mr. (Box 6)
      - Hewson, Al (Box 6)
      - Johnson, Dot (Box 6)
      - Kleeb, Bev (Box 6)
      - Launching Chrysler (Box 6)
      - Musgrave, Richard J. (Box 6)
      - Northville Labs (Box 6)
      - Northville Lumber (Box 6)
      - South Lyon Church of Christ (Box 6)
      - South Lyon State Savings (Box 6)
      - Truance, Irma and Sam (Box 6)
      - Zahti, Inga (Box 6)
    - 1978-1982
      - Broadway Old Town (Box 6)
      - Carolina Tire (Box 6)
      - Howell Red Band Motors (Box 6)
      - Keating, Norm (Box 6)
      - Little Caesers (Box 6)
      - Northville Lab (Box 6)
      - Quanex Executive Ports (Box 6)
      - South Lyon School Bands (Box 6)
      - South Lyon State Bank (Box 6)
      - Westerman, Charlie (Box 6)
      - Wigg, Stephanie (Box 6)
    - 1983-1985
      - Anderson, Mary (Box 6)
      - Andrews, Lisa (Box 6)
      - Caldwell, Richard (Box 6)
      - Dillingham, Fred (Box 6)
      - Ellis, Joe (Box 6)
      - Oldford Family (Box 6)
      - Grant, Carol and Percy (Box 6)
      - Kleeb, Rustex (Box 6)
      - Lawrence-Anderson, Katherine (Box 6)
      - Meavs, James (Box 6)
      - Wagner, Robert (Box 6)
    - 1986
      - Andrews, Carol (Box 7)
      - Bittell (Box 7)
      - Brandenburg, Linda (Box 7)
      - Brighton High School Faculty (Box 7)
      - Chouinard, Kathy (Box 7)
      - DeCocq, Paul (Box 7)
      - Foust, Ardie (Box 7)
      - Fazekis, Frank (Box 7)
      - Grant, Carol (Box 7)
      - Green, Tom and Pam (Box 7)
      - Ivkovich, Steve and Jenny (Box 7)
      - Miller, Dr. Steven (Box 7)
      - Oldford, Grant (Box 7)
      - Perelli Family (Box 7)
      - Peters, Jill (Box 7)
      - Pupilis, Elain and Charles (Box 7)
      - Robertson, James (Family) (Box 7)
      - Work, Fred and Lucas (Box 7)
    - 1987
      - Baum, Mike and Karen (Box 7)
      - Bishop, Marianne (Box 7)
      - Hartland Music Hall (Box 7)
      - Kleeb -- Model of Cayman House (Box 7)
      - Klimanicz, Phil (Box 7)
      - May & Scofield (Box 7)
      - Nicholas, JT (Box 7)
      - Pollard, Howard and Barbara (Box 7)
      - Reed, Sue (Box 7)
      - Reiland, Jack (Box 7)
      - Trinas Friend with Horse (Box 7)
    - 1988
      - Anderson, Tom (Box 7)
      - Bender, Leonard (Box 7)
      - Clausnitzer, Jack (Box 7)
      - Davis, Harry and Carol (Box 7)
      - Hartland Music Hall (Box 7)
      - Klimanicz, Phil (Box 7)
      - Kunkle, Sandy (Box 7)
      - Nicholas, J.T. (Box 7)
      - Scott, Robert (Box 7)
      - Stanger, Auld (Box 7)
      - Steve and Friends (Box 7)
    - 1989
      - Anderson, Catherine (Box 7)
      - Brown, Harry (Box 7)
      - Gaintier, Michelle (Box 7)
      - Galbraith, James (Box 7)
      - Galbraith, Steve (Box 7)
      - Johnston, Sarah (Box 7)
      - Murphy, Blanch (Box 7)
      - Oldford, Brett (Box 7)
      - Oldford, Stu (Box 7)
      - Shenandoah Shop (Box 7)
      - Spicer, Alan (Box 7)
    - 1990
      - Bender, Dr. Leonard (Box 7)
      - Britus (Box 7)
      - Brown, Harry (Box 7)
      - Campbell, Paul (Box 7)
      - Davis, Harry and Carol (Box 7)
      - Evans, Yurata (Box 7)
      - Franchy, Steve (Box 7)
      - Jaques (Box 7)
      - McKay, Marian (Box 7)
      - Rufferity, Tony (Box 7)
      - Spicer, Alan (Box 7)
      - Webster, Sandra (Box 7)
    - 1991-1993
      - Calkins, Kingsley and Jo (Box 7)
      - Cromaine Library (Box 7)
      - Galbraith, James (Box 7)
      - Galbraith, Susan (Box 7)
      - Hagerman, Bert (Box 7)
      - MacKay, Basil (Box 7)
      - McIntyre, Elenor (Box 7)
      - Mersereau, Darryl (Box 7)
      - Nestor, Lu (Box 7)
      - Otis, Amy (Box 7)
    - Undated
      - Abbey, Amy (Box 7)
      - Adler, Tom (Box 7)
      - Allmand, Douglas (Box 7)
      - Anderson, Bev (Box 7)
      - Anderson, Gary (Box 7)
      - Anderson, Mary (Box 7)
      - Armstrong, Harold (Box 7)
      - Arnow, Harriet (Box 7)
      - Atchison, Dr. (Box 7)
      - Aydlott, Linda and Jeremy (Box 7)
      - Barrett, Carolyn (Box 7)
      - Beaty, RC. (Box 7)
      - Beltz, Mary Ann (Box 7)
      - Benson Horse (Box 7)
      - Beauregard, Marie (Box 7)
      - Bishop, Marranine (Box 7)
      - Bittell, Sue and Art (Box 7)
      - Borth, Vange (Box 7)
      - Briston, David (Box 7)
      - Bulloch, Robert (Box 7)
      - Burgess, Gerald (Box 7)
      - Burley, John (Box 7)
      - Callahan, Roy (Box 7)
      - Campan, Robert (Box 7)
      - Caroselli, Pete (Box 7)
      - Carr, Bob (Box 7)
      - Cartwright Family (Box 7)
      - Cavey, Joe (Box 7)
      - Christensen, Dennis (Box 7)
      - Clark, Joe (Box 7)
      - Clawson, Suogoda (Box 7)
      - Clements, Sean (Box 7)
      - Cook, Perry (Box 7)
      - Cornell, Phyllis (Box 7)
      - Cowan, Judy and Gerry (Box 7)
      - Crouse Family Reunion (Box 7)
      - Davis, John (Box 7)
      - Day, Jim (Box 7)
      - Devitt, Annette (Box 7)
      - Dillingham, Fred (Box 7)
      - Dingler, Robert (Box 7)
      - Donovan, Ray (Box 7)
      - Dormire, James (Box 7)
      - Dunleavy, Margaret (Box 7)
      - Dunsmore, Ira (Box 7)
      - Eckman, Andy and Family (Box 7)
      - Ellis, Joe (Box 7)
      - Epley, Don and Eunice (Box 7)
      - Essenburg, Rev. Glenn (Box 7)
      - Faulds, Rob (Box 7)
      - Faust, Charlie (Box 7)
      - Foldernauer, Joe and Eva (Box 7)
      - Forrer, Jane (Box 7)
      - Franks Family Restaurant (Passelaqua) (Box 7)
      - Franks Parity Store (Box 7)
      - Gaines, Bonita (Box 8)
      - Galbraith, Sue and Jim (Box 8)
      - Galloway, John (Box 8)
      - Gee, David (Box 8)
      - George, Jim (Box 8)
      - Germane, James (Box 8)
      - Glenn, Mrs. B. H. (Box 8)
      - Goetz, John and Mary (Box 8)
      - Goodman, Mr. (?) (Box 8)
      - Grant, Carol (Box 8)
      - Gray, Ed (Box 8)
      - Green, Tom and Pam (Box 8)
      - Gregor, John (Box 8)
      - Haan, Charlie (Box 8)
      - Halliday, Shirley (Box 8)
      - Hamway, Irene and Tom (Box 8)
      - Hamway, Stella (Box 8)
      - Hards, Marian (Box 8)
      - Haviland, Nancy (Box 8)
      - Hilbert, Scott (Box 8)
      - Horst, Cindy (Box 8)
      - Hultberg, Frank and Sherry (Box 8)
      - Huskinson, Eva (Box 8)
      - Jajo, Sami Zia (Box 8)
      - Jarvis, James (Box 8)
      - Jones, Jim (Box 8)
      - Junne, Geo (Box 8)
      - Kazmevzak, Tom (Box 8)
      - Keating, Norm (Box 8)
      - Kirsch, Bill and Helen (Box 8)
      - Kleeb, Robert and Bev (Box 8)
      - Klimowicz, Phil (Box 8)
      - Komlos, Valerie (Box 8)
      - Kniaz, Tony (Box 8)
      - Kunkle, Sandy (Box 8)
      - Lapinski, Jeff (Box 8)
      - Lawrence, Katherine (Box 8)
      - Litzenburg, Lou (Box 8)
      - Lyons, Herbert (Box 8)
      - MacKay, Marion (Box 8)
      - Macomber, Barb (Box 8)
      - McBride, Robert (Box 8)
      - McCall, Rae Ann (Box 8)
      - McClintock, Bil (Box 8)
      - McCriery, Bill (Box 8)
      - McEachern, Bill (Box 8)
      - McIntyre (?) (Box 8)
      - Mears, Terry (Box 8)
      - Meister, Kurt (Box 8)
      - Mike, Joe (Box 8)
      - Mitten, Robin (Box 8)
      - Minneker, Tom (Box 8)
      - Mitchell Family (Box 8)
      - Morgan, Bert and Nellie (Box 8)
      - Morningstar, Gersh (Box 8)
      - Nestor, Lulu (Box 8)
      - Nichols, Sandy (Box 8)
      - Oldford, Brett (Box 8)
      - Parshall, Arvilla (Box 8)
      - Pellitier, Bill (Box 8)
      - Porrittee, Elizabeth (Box 8)
      - Richards, Irene (Box 8)
      - Rizor, Lysle (Box 8)
      - Roe, Mildred (Box 8)
      - Russells, Bull Session (?) (Box 8)
      - Schleah, Pat (Box 8)
      - Sherba, Sandy (Box 8)
      - Shields, Judy (Box 8)
      - Soley, Theo and Sylvia (Box 8)
      - Sparrow, Tom (Box 8)
      - Spaw, Rev. Mark (Box 8)
      - Steinacker, Wilbur and Family (Box 8)
      - Strong, Romaine (Box 8)
      - Stubbs, Jack (Box 8)
      - Sweet, Nancy (Box 8)
      - Sweeton, Diana (Box 8)
      - Taylor, Vesa (Box 8)
      - Tenaglia, Chris (Box 8)
      - Tice, Albert and Juanita (Box 8)
      - Thompson, Rev. Thomas (Box 8)
      - Toma, David (Box 8)
      - Waddles, Mother (Box 8)
      - Wagner, Peg (Box 8)
      - Wakeman, Robert (Box 8)
      - Walker, Marion (Box 8)
      - Wesler, Karl (Family) (Box 8)
      - Wilkinson, Charles (Box 8)
      - Willacker, Stan (Box 8)
      - Wilson, Lillian (Box 8)
      - Wilson, Mike (Box 8)
      - Wyckott, Bill (Box 8)
      - Wyckott, Forest (Box 8)
      - Wyckott, Marjorie (Box 8)
      - Zotto (?) (Box 8)
    - Unidentified and undated, 9 folders (Box 9)
  - Commissions and Events
    - Ypsilanti Greek Theater 1963-1968, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Dudley Randall 1971 (Box 9)
    - Celebrations and Conventions 1971-1976 (Box 9)
    - Memorial Day 1979, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Ann Arbor Farmer's Market 1982 (Box 9)
    - Trips to Oregon and Bob-Lo 1986 (Box 9)
    - Gazette Photos, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - Walter Reuther and Arthur Miller undated (Box 9)
    - Benny Goodman undated (Box 9)
    - Aaron Copland undated (Box 9)
    - Ruby Dee undated (Box 9)
    - Bert Lahr undated (Box 9)
    - Andrés Segovia undated (Box 9)
    - (see oversize) (Box 9)
  - Life in Michigan
    - Farm and Steam Festival undated (Box 9)
    - Prints undated, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous undated, 5 folders (Box 10)
- Oversize